Jonathan García

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Phone: +593939599861 **Email:** jonfrgar@espol.edu.ec

Web: https://elpitagoras14.github.io/

Address: Guayaquil, Ecuador

I am a FullStack Developer with 2 years of experience in the Industry and studies in Computer Science Engineering. I have worked in many projects, both in Frontend and Backend development, and I have also done some DevOps tasks. My skills include English, Photoshop, Javascript, CSS, HTML, Clojure, Java, NodeJS, Express, GIT, AWS, Redis, MySQL, MongoDB, Python. I am also passionate about Reading, Videogames, Music, Philosophy, Anime, and Coding.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Algorithm analysis academic assistant | ESPOL

May. 2022 - Jan. 2023

• Design and development of algorithm analysis classes, resolution of exercises and answering questions to students.

Software Development Intern | Dátil

Feb. 2022 - May. 2022

- Development of new electronic billing functions and solution of reported problems.
- Developed software currently in production.
- Making changes (fixing/upgrading) to existing applications.

Backend Developer | Shippify

Sep. 2022 - Jan. 2023

- Developed software using a variety of programming languages, including Java, JavaScript, and Node.js
- Wrote code to create applications that meet customer needs and business objectives
- Tested software to ensure it meets specifications and is free of defects
- Deployed software to production systems and provided support to users

EDUCATION

Computer Science Engineering | ESPOL

May. 2019 - Present

- Developed an understanding of computer science concepts and their applications
- · Worked with different programming languages to create software applications
- Learned how to design and implement algorithms to solve problems
- Gained experience in working with databases and networks

SKILLS

English

• HTML

Express

MySQL

Photoshop

Clojure

• GIT

MongoDB

Javascript

Java

AWS

Python

• CSS

NodeJS

Redis

HOBBIES

Reading

Videogames

Music

Anime